Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers GEN MSS 996
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Computer media, 1994-2005; 5; 706028; 4 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  This series chiefly consists of the electronic files created by Morath. The electronic files consist of image files and backup files, as well as operating system and utility program files used by Morath. The series also includes Morath's computer and an external disk drive unit.
  The Inge Morath Foundation created some of the electronic files in this series.
  - DVDs, 706175
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&87a90210-2eef-485d-9bca-175c3d9545a9
    - Arthur Miller HOWARD GREENBERG GALLERY MAY 26, 2004, 2014-genam-5-0001; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&29c5c97d-141c-47d0-9c0e-7e19ef7878d9
    - The Misfits Tape #2 Inge Morath Interview 5/16/01 w/Burn in T.C., 2014-genam-5-0002; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3f9351f1-e720-489d-9869-0fbe086d2bb7
    - The Misfits Tape #3 Inge Morath Interview 5/16/01 w/Burn in T.C., 2014-genam-5-0003; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&def9c5b3-54be-45fa-8a65-759687654467
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0004; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c533cf7d-99a8-4908-97b6-01ccbd9f64a2
    - UNIVERSITY OF CONNECTICUT Litchfield County Writers Project & Uconn Torrington Campus John Jacob Inge Morath's book, The Road to Reno November 26, 2007, 2014-genam-5-0005; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e1df9d02-6243-4b6a-92eb-5b087b481669
    - MORATH--ROMANIA ORIGINAL RGB, PRESSE, WEB, 2014-genam-5-0006; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6e1d0966-3298-4575-b568-dab2b666e599
    - Backup #1 7/7/05, 2014-genam-5-0007; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bde737ad-3601-45a0-9d94-3f016f412bc0
    - Backup #2 7/7/05, 2014-genam-5-0008; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&12eb6a48-2348-4a94-9f61-9184dd7be373
    - Backup with Sebastian Leftover files on computer 8/9/05, 2014-genam-5-0009; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8497c2ca-7572-4b9a-a159-66f53a056f95
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0010; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b4716b76-4398-414c-a111-0415bf7a0e01
    - Captions_1959_1960, 2014-genam-5-0011; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5eb5b6b1-09b1-4952-b3ff-051ac1832d0a
    - Captions_61_65, 2014-genam-5-0012; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&189abd66-0e34-48f3-a373-445c02e6348d
    - Captions_66_75, 2014-genam-5-0013; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0d50fd45-8777-4d49-927a-dc436ad8ce62
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0193; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 725)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&499a9da0-3591-4f90-bd02-079cdfc4b254
  - Floppy Disks, 706171
    - Computer utility programs, 1994-1996; 706174
      - EPSON Scanner Utility Program for Macintosh Version 2.0aA Program Disk 1, 2014-genam-5-0014; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - EPSON Scanner Utility Program for Macintosh Version 2.0aA Program Disk 2, 2014-genam-5-0015; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - EPSON Driver Disk 1, 2014-genam-5-0016; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - EPSON Driver Disk 2, 2014-genam-5-0017; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - Disk Doctor, 2014-genam-5-0018; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - DaynaPORT INSTALLATION DISK, 2014-genam-5-0019; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - GoType! PRO, 2014-genam-5-0020; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - ADAPTEC SCSI SELECT v1.0, 2014-genam-5-0021; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - MacComCenter fax and data communications, 2014-genam-5-0022; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - Polaroid SprintScan Plug-in Module, 2014-genam-5-0023; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - Polaroid SprintScan Apple Shared Library Manager, 2014-genam-5-0024; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - CLARIS FOR MACINTOSH Disk 1 FileMaker PRO, 2014-genam-5-0025; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - CLARIS FOR MACINTOSH Disk 2 FileMaker PRO, 2014-genam-5-0026; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
      - CLARIS FOR MACINTOSH Disk 3 FileMaker PRO, 2014-genam-5-0027; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - Inge's captions Moi.TXT PC, 2014-genam-5-0028; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0029; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0030; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0031; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0032; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0033; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0034; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0035; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0036; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0037; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0038; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0039; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0040; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0041; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0042; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0043; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0044; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0045; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0046; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0047; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0048; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0049; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0050; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0051; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - inge bio master list, 2014-genam-5-0052; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0053; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
    - Mt Morgan.1, 2014-genam-5-0054; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 726)
  - Orb Disk, 2014-genam-5-0055; 706169; 1 Computer Storage Media Orb Disk (Box 727)
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&339c2ce8-a4b6-41df-a08c-ddca3ac8ec0b
  - Zip Disks, 706155
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4d6c4e43-3c18-41a9-bb72-daa2545b42a3
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0056; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09d0907c-9e89-41da-abab-5264df8a66b4
    - Inge Database backup, 2014-genam-5-0057; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8e382427-0e25-42be-acf9-6b0e87b69b4a
    - Captions Back-up, 2014-genam-5-0058; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&480537f9-c9cd-4175-8e90-4ff2044021a8
    - Inge's Word Process. Back-up 11/97, 2014-genam-5-0059; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&13937bf0-c13a-45e3-b071-e38b02f8f6c1
    - Database backups, 2014-genam-5-0060; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3896b80a-86e6-4c16-a276-186dd19058cf
    - Sys 8 1, 2014-genam-5-0061; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09c826c5-ef8a-4b48-9f1d-19191b35b6a0
    - Sys 8 2, 2014-genam-5-0062; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7f5c3159-2962-4222-9215-4a92a26d9aaa
    - Inga's DATA, 2014-genam-5-0063; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&189d08c4-e1ff-425a-a64f-8f67da9bb570
    - Inge Morath Preliminary Client Version Macintosh 9/20/98, 2014-genam-5-0064; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f96a9b8e-add9-4468-b79a-cea563761275
    - File BAK 12/99 Inge Word Processing, 2014-genam-5-0065; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&92b8faab-9e69-4fe2-8484-f86ec5b90e8b
    - System Back-up 11/97, 2014-genam-5-0066; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0029a3b5-6d6d-4a13-b189-138f68f961b1
    - inge File BAK 5-2-00, 2014-genam-5-0067; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&60e08aca-2ea4-493d-bef2-4fc6ed989824
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0068; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 727)
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&48f2edc7-e2d7-4e6d-82ca-4b0151708556
  - Compact Discs, 706030
    - "Various scans: Masks, Slovenia, Venice...", 706064
      - M0I SAUL BOX 1-1, 2014-genam-5-0136; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I SAUL BOX 1-2, 2014-genam-5-0137; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I saul steinberg box 2-1, 2014-genam-5-0138; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I Saul 2-2, 2014-genam-5-0139; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I Saul box 2-3, 2014-genam-5-0140; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I color sleve 1-1, 2014-genam-5-0141; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - M0I COLOR sleve 1-2, 2014-genam-5-0142; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLORSLEVE 2-1 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0143; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLORSLEVE 2-2 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0144; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLOR SLEVE 3-1 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0145; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLOR SLEVE 3-2, 2014-genam-5-0146; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLOR SLEVE 4-1 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0147; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - colorsleve 4-2 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0148; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - COLORSLEVE 5-1 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0149; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - colorsleve 5-2 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0150; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - Color Sleve 6-1 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0151; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - colorsleve6 6-2 M0I, 2014-genam-5-0152; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - Saul Steinburg Mask Series, 2014-genam-5-0153; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - Children of Difference, 2014-genam-5-0154; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - Columbia, 2014-genam-5-0155; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
      - 1955 Venice Inge Morath Disc #1, 2014-genam-5-0156; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - 1955 Venice Inge Morath Disc #2, 2014-genam-5-0157; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Slovenia Part 1 For: Honor Moore, 2014-genam-5-0158; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Slovenia Part 2 For: Honor Moore, 2014-genam-5-0159; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
    - Arthur Miller, 706032
      "Arthur Miller theatre scans"
      - Death of a Salesman, 706037
        - Salesman in Beijing 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0176; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman in Beijing 2 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0177; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman in Beijing Behind the scenes 2, 2014-genam-5-0179; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman - Stockholm 05/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0180; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman - Movie w Dustin Misc., 2014-genam-5-0181; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman + Hoffman 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0182; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman + Hoffman Behind the scenes Promo 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0183; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman + Hoffman 2 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0184; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman + Hoffman Filming 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0185; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
        - Salesman in Beijing Behind the Scenes 5/13/03, 2014-genam-5-0178; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
          Unable to virus scan
          Media is unreadable and could not be scanned for malicious files. Content capture was not attempted.
      - Arthur Miller 1, 2014-genam-5-0163; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - AM2, 2014-genam-5-0164; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - AM3, 2014-genam-5-0165; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - AM 4, 2014-genam-5-0166; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Inge Morath Crucible 2002, 2014-genam-5-0167; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - After The Fall 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0168; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - After The Fall -Behind 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0169; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - American Clock Archbishop's Ceiling Broken Glass Memory of 2 Mondays Focus 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0170; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Creation of the World, 2014-genam-5-0171; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Creation of the World -Behind, 2014-genam-5-0172; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - The Crucible 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0173; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Incident at Vichy -Behind Mr. Peter's Connections 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0174; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - The Price 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0175; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Up From Paradise 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0187; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - NBC - plays 5/9/03, 2014-genam-5-0188; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0189; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0191; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0192; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0194; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - Akik idejöttek Magyarország a külföldi fotográfusok kamerája előtt Taken in Hungary A Country Mirrored by Foreign Photographers, 2014-genam-5-0186; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
      - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0190; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
    - Mac System folder & Utilities 4.02, 2014-genam-5-0108; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Database backup August 9, 2005, 2014-genam-5-0109; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - morath database 2/9/05, 2014-genam-5-0110; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - imdatabase back up 12/16/04, 2014-genam-5-0111; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - May 5, 2005 Morath database, 2014-genam-5-0112; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Morath database 3/24/05, 2014-genam-5-0113; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - April 2, 2004, 2014-genam-5-0114; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - June 17, 2004, 2014-genam-5-0115; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Morath Foundation 11/19/03 Databases + Exel, 2014-genam-5-0116; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Final Database, 2014-genam-5-0117; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - IM database back up 1/6/05, 2014-genam-5-0118; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Database 11/14/04, 2014-genam-5-0119; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - database b/u 8/25/04, 2014-genam-5-0120; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - database backup 08/17/04, 2014-genam-5-0121; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - database backup 09/09/04, 2014-genam-5-0122; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - IM Database 10/28/04, 2014-genam-5-0123; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - LaCie Toast v4.0.2 Standard Edition for Macintosh, 2014-genam-5-0124; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - LaCie EasyCD Creation v4.02L for Windows DirectCD v3.01L for Windows, 2014-genam-5-0125; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - hp jetdirect cd-rom, 2014-genam-5-0126; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Software Drivers Macintosh & PC Compatible CD-ROM Delkin Devices, 2014-genam-5-0127; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Mac OS8, 2014-genam-5-0128; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Verizon Online DSL, 2014-genam-5-0129; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - EPSON Expression 836XL Scanning Tools, 2014-genam-5-0130; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - SilverFast Epson Scanner, 2014-genam-5-0131; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - CHINA EXHIBIT, 2014-genam-5-0132; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - misfits slide images, 2014-genam-5-0133; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Im database backup 6/15/05, 2014-genam-5-0134; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - M0I, 2014-genam-5-0135; 1 CD-Rs (Box 729)
    - Red Shoes, 2014-genam-5-0160; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
    - Digital Dream Multimedia BAK Inventory solution 10/29/03 A, 2014-genam-5-0161; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
    - Digital Dream Multimedia BAK Inventory solution 10/22/03 A, 2014-genam-5-0162; 1 CD-Rs (Box 730)
    - backup 11.07.03, 2014-genam-5-0069; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 11.13.03, 2014-genam-5-0070; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 12.01.03, 2014-genam-5-0071; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 12.04.03, 2014-genam-5-0072; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 12.11.03, 2014-genam-5-0073; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 12.18.03, 2014-genam-5-0074; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 11.20.03, 2014-genam-5-0075; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge File BAK 6/15/01 1 of 2 1. All Files (wp), 2014-genam-5-0076; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge File BAK 6/15/01 2 of 2 2. Database, 2014-genam-5-0077; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Morath File BAK Database, Files, system 9/7/00, 2014-genam-5-0078; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files + Desktop 12_22_00, 2014-genam-5-0079; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge File BAK 2_17_01, 2014-genam-5-0080; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - MOI BAK 1_27_01 Files, 2014-genam-5-0081; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files BAK 1_5_01, 2014-genam-5-0082; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files 9-17-00, 2014-genam-5-0083; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files + Desktop BAK 11/20/00, 2014-genam-5-0084; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files BAK 12/1/00, 2014-genam-5-0085; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Morath File BAK Database, Files, system, 2014-genam-5-0086; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - 2001001D Ronan's B'day, 2014-genam-5-0087; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - 9/26/01 Digital camera + Database, 2014-genam-5-0088; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Morath IBM Client Version 1.0, 2014-genam-5-0089; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Database 8/13/01, 2014-genam-5-0090; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files BAK Disc 1 of 2 3/19/01, 2014-genam-5-0091; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Files BAK Disc 2 of 2 3/19/01, 2014-genam-5-0092; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge BAK 7/18/01 DataBase, 2014-genam-5-0093; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - Inge Morath Macintosh Client Version 1.0, 2014-genam-5-0094; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 3.11.04, 2014-genam-5-0095; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 3.4.04, 2014-genam-5-0096; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 1.22.04, 2014-genam-5-0097; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 2.5.04, 2014-genam-5-0098; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 2.11.04, 2014-genam-5-0099; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 2.19.04, 2014-genam-5-0100; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 2.25.04, 2014-genam-5-0101; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 01.15.04, 2014-genam-5-0102; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 1.8.04, 2014-genam-5-0103; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 8.2.04, 2014-genam-5-0104; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 3.25.04, 2014-genam-5-0105; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 5-13-04, 2014-genam-5-0106; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
    - backup 4/29/04, 2014-genam-5-0107; 1 CD-Rs (Box 728)
  - Computer, Motorola StarMax, 706029
    General
    Beinecke has removed and retained the internal hard drive from the Motorola StarMax 3000 / 160 Power PC desktop computer originally included in this collection. The rest of the machine has been deaccessioned.
    - [no label information], 2014-genam-5-0195; 1 Internal Hard Drives; 15303075840 bytes 15.3 Gigabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 732)
  - Microtech Digital PhotoAlbum Card Reader, undated; 706031; 1 Items card reader and cords (Box 731)
- Objects, 1954-2000; 6; 706019; 1.94 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
  Series VI is organized into two subseries: Photography Related and Personal Effects.
  This series consists of the items Morath used as a photographer, including a camera, film canisters, and rubber ink stamps used to mark her prints, as well as other personal effects, including scarves and a suitcase.
  - Photography Related, 706023
    - Leica M3 camera, circa 1954; 706027 (Box 733)
    - Film canisters, undated; 706026; 40 Items (Box 734)
    - Film canisters, undated; 706025; 29 Items (Box 735)
    - Rubber stamps, undated; 706024; 18 Items (Box 736)
      Morath used the rubber stamps to mark her photographic prints
  - Personal Effects, 706020
    - Silk scarves, undated; 706022; 2 Items (Box 737)
    - Black suitcase, undated; 706021 (Box 738)
- Printed Material, 1952-2002; 705986; 20.92 Linear Feet (18 boxes)
  Printed material is chiefly organized into two groups: Travel, Language and Ephemera and General Books. It also includes Material Found in Books and The Last Journey portfolio.
  Printed material consists of books, periodicals, and other published material by or about Morath and her work, as well as travel and language books used by her.
  - Travel, Language, and Ephemera Publications, 706006
    This group of printed material consists of Morath's travel guides, language books, maps and ephemera.
    - Printed material, 706018 (Box 739)
    - Printed material, 706017 (Box 740)
    - Printed material, 706016 (Box 741)
    - Printed material, 706015 (Box 742)
    - Printed material, 706014 (Box 743)
    - Printed material, 706013 (Box 744)
    - Printed material, 706012 (Box 745)
    - Printed material, 706011 (Box 746)
    - Printed material, 706010 (Box 747)
    - Printed material, 706009 (Box 748)
    - Printed material, 706008 (Box 749)
    - Printed material, 706007 (Box 750 (Oversize))
    - Printed material, 1971-1993; undated; 4 Folders (Box 755)
      Includes Russia, a handbook, Costa da morte, Dehio wien, and Walhalla.
    - Printed material, 1966-1999; 5 Folders (Box 756)
      Includes Fodor's guide to Japan and East Asia, Hisorias de la Iglesia de Navalcan, Knoph guide to Venice, Illustrated guide to Dehli, Agra, and Jaipur, and Guía práctica del peregrino El Camino de Santiago.
    - Printed material, 1988-1993; undated; 4 Folders (Box 757)
      Includes Knaurs Kulturführer in fabre in Donau, Penguid guide to ancient Egypt, El Camino de Santiago, and Santiago de compostela Corña.
    - Printed material, 2000-2003; undated; 7 Folders (Box 758)
      Includes calendars, cards, and address book: Women, Photographs from Magnum Photos, Magnum Photos, Agenda, Agenda Club Cultura, Eddy specialty papers Magnum Photos, and Magnum Photos.
  - Material from Books, 706005; 6 Folders (Box 751)
    This group of material consists of notes, maps, postcards, book inserts, brochures, and other printed items found in or filed with books.
  - The Last Journey portfolio, 2001; 2004; 706004 (Box 752 (Oversize))
    The Last Journey is a limited edition portfolio created by Branko Lenart that consists of sixteen photographs of Morath and in remembrance of her. A letter to Arthur Miller from Branko Lenart accompanied the portfolio and describes its creation. This portfolio is number two of ten
  - General Books, 705987
    Books, periodicals, and other printed material about Morath and her work.
    - Books, 706003
    - Books, 706002
    - Books, 706001
    - Books, 706000
    - Books, 705999
    - Books, 705998
    - Books, 705997
    - Books, 705996
    - Books, 705995
    - Books, 705994
    - Books, 705993
    - Books, 705992
    - Books, 705991
    - Books, 705990
    - Books, 705989
    - Books, 705988
- December 2018 Acquisition, circa 1970; 7; 6.08 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
  Gift of Rebecca Miller, 2018.
  This addition consists of two artworks by Olga Carlisle, given to Inge Morath by the artist.
  - Untitled oil painting, circa 1970; Carlisle, Olga Andreyev (Box 753 (Oversize))
    Custodial History
    This painting previously hung in Inge Morath and Arthur Miller's apartment in New York City.
  - Ink drawing inscribed to Inge Morath, circa 1970; Carlisle, Olga Andreyev (Box 754 (Oversize))
    This drawing previously hung in Inge Morath and Arthur Miller's barn at their home in Roxbury, Connecticut.
- April 2018 Acquisition, 1910–2003; 8; 138.34 Linear Feet (73 boxes) + 1 art, 8 broadside